// ConsoleApplication1.cpp : This file contains the 'main' function. Program execution begins and ends there.
//

#include "pch.h"
#include <iostream>

int main()
{
    std::cout << "Hello World!\n"; 
}

		// Run program: Ctrl + F5 or Debug > Start Without Debugging menu
		// Debug program: F5 or Debug > Start Debugging menu

        // Tips for Getting Started: 
        //   1. Use the Solution Explorer window to add/manage files
        //   2. Use the Team Explorer window to connect to source control
        //   3. Use the Output window to see build output and other messages
        //   4. Use the Error List window to view errors
        //   5. Go to Project > Add New Item to create new code files, or Project > Add Existing Item to add existing code files to the project
        //   6. In the future, to open this project again, go to File > Open > Project and select the .sln file
